Guide to the Reston Community Association Planning and Zoning Committee records, 1961-1997
George Mason University Libraries
Special Collections and Archives, George Mason University
Reston Community Association Planning and Zoning Committee records
1961-1997
George Mason University. Special Collections and Archives.
John T. Dockery
C0143
13 linear feet 25 boxes
The collection documents the time that John Dockery served on the Reston Community Association Planning and Zoning Committee. John Dockery worked on the committee from the 1970s into the 1980s. Most of the documents are dated in the 1970s with a few in the 1960s, 1980s and 1990s. The documents are memos, blueprints, maps and other paperwork involved in the running of the committee.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
Donated in 2004 by John Dockery.
Biographical Information
Reston is a planned community in Northern Virginia. Robert E. Simon, Jr. was the founder of Reston, and he purchased the land with the proceeds from the sale of Carnegie Hall in New York City in 1961. Construction began in 1963 with the building of Lake Anne. Simon wanted Reston to be a place where individuals could remain their entire lives, thus many different types of housing were constructed. In 1968 the Reston Community Association (RCA) was created to take responsibility for community programs. John Dockery served on the Reston Community Association Planning and Zoning Committee from the 1970s to the early 1980s. During that time the Reston Community Association was incorporated with the Reston Homeowners Association under the name Reston Association.
Scope and Content
The collection documents the time that John Dockery served on the Reston Community Association Planning and Zoning Committee. John Dockery worked on the committee from the 1970s into the 1990s. Most of the documents are dated in the 1970s with a few in the 1960s, 1980s and 1990s. The documents include memos, blueprints, maps and other paperwork involved in the running of the committee.
The documents are organized into two series. The series one consists of subject files arranged in alphabetical order. Documents with the same title are then organized into chronological order. The documents all relate to the Reston Community Association Planning and Zoning Committee.
Series two consists of documents arranged in chronological order. Some of the documents titles are similar to series one while others are merely titled with the project number. All of these documents relate to planning and zoning projects in Reston.
Arrangement
Organized into one series.
Series 1: Subject Files, 1961-1980 (Boxes 1-11)
Series 2: Chronological Files, 1965-1997 (12-25)
Adjunct Descriptive Data
Related Material
The Special Collections and Archives also holds the Planned Community Archives and other personal papers and organizational records that document Reston, Virginia, and other planned communities.
Index Terms
Corporate Names:
Reston Community Association.
Geographical Names:
Reston (Va.)
Subjects:
Housing--Virginia--Reston.; Planned communities--Virginia--Reston.; Zoning--Virginia--Reston.
Contents List
- Series 1: Subject Files, 1961-1980; (11 boxes)
  The documents include maps, planning documents, memoranda, correspondence, legal documents and other related material. There are eleven boxes with the documents organized alphabetically.
  - Ad Hoc Committee: Impact of Air noise from Dulles Airport, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    3.19
  - Addendum to Reston Community Association to Planning Commission on Reviewed Case no. C-387, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    11.18
  - Adoption of Amendment to Chapter 30 of the Code of Fairfax County, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    1.03
  - Adoption of Amendment to Chapter 30, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    3.03
  - Agenda of Fairfax County Planning Commission, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    5.05
  - Agenda from the Board of Appeals, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    5.43
  - Amendments and Proposals, 1972-1974 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    6.22
  - American Institute of Planners Conference, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    11.06
  - American General, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    4.14
  - Application for Permit to Erect, Alter or Relocate Sign, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    4.33
  - Architectural Board of Review, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    11.01
  - Basis of Reston Home Owners Association Assessments, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    3.11
  - Basic Services: Water, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    1.05
  - Beltway Issues, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    6.04
  - Bidding Notices, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    10.07
  - Bid Plan Room Report by Northern Virginia Builders Association, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    6.08
  - Blue Ridge Aerial Survey Photographs, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    5.47
  - Board of Supervisors Application, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    4.07
  - Brief History of Reston, Virginia and Inside Reston, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    1.11
  - Building Sites, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    7.13
  - Bylaws, Deed of Dedication Articles of Incorporation of the Reston Second Home Owners Association, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    2.08
  - Capital Improvement Program (Map), 1976-1980 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    11.19
  - Chapter 30 and Amendment Code, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    5.01
  - Circuit Court of Loundoun County: Levitt and Sons vs. The Board of Supervisors of Loundoun County, Virginia, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    1.13
  - Clinch Corporation Application, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    4.08
  - Cluster Site, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    10.10
  - Columbia Conference on Community Governance, First Annual, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    1.15
  - Committee on Taxation and Assessments, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    3.12
  - Common Land Between Lots 12 and 13, Section 6, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    2.09
  - Community Development Evaluation Series No. 2: Citizen Participation in the Model Cities Program, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    7.06
  - Correspondence with Martha Pennino, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    11.09
  - Correspondence from Morton W. Noble, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    10.06
  - Correspondence REgarding Winter Site Plan, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    10.14
  - County 5 Year Plan, Approved by Board of Supervisors, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    10.08
  - Cover letter for Block 1, Section 32, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    8.08
  - Decree Invalidating Fairfax County low/moderate-income and Amendments to the Zoning Ordinance, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    10.17
  - Delineation of Small Areas, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    2.16
  - Denials of Upper Potomac Planning Case, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    4.28
  - Density Control under Residential Planned Community Chapter of Fairfax County, Zoning Ordinance, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    10.12
  - Department of County Development, Advertising the Land Use Tax for Public Hearing, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    1.10
  - Development of Walkways and Pedestrian Grade Separations in Reston, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    5.48
  - Development of A-502, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    10.15
  - District I-L, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    11.04
  - Division of Design Review Weekly Summary, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    8.05
  - Division of Design Review Weekly Summaries, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    8.03
  - Division of Design Review Weekly Summary, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    8.04
  - Draft Resolution for Consideration by the Fairfax County Board of Supervisors, 1970s (Box 4, Folder 2)
    5.10
  - Existing Land Use and Existing Zoning in Fairfax County, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    3.07
  - Fairfax Newsletter, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    5.44
  - Fairfax Newsletter, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    6.13
  - Fairfax County, Public Facilities (Schools and Parks), 1972 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    4.32
  - Fairfax County, Public Hearing, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    3.08
  - Five Year Plan, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    9.11
  - Flow Chart: "Unclassified", 1973 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    9.06
  - Foxmill Park Hearing, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    11.03
  - Gala Holiday Happening Flyer, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    10.04
  - The Globe, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    6.06
  - Government Executive, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    4.13
  - Gulf Reston, Incorporation Application to Development Plan Amendment to B-230, 1970s (Box 4, Folder 14)
    5.32
  - Gulf of Reston Incorporation vs. Board of Supervisors, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    10.16
  - Gulf Reston Incorporation Application C-432, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    4.31
  - How Does Rezoning Work, 1970s (Box 4, Folder 18)
    5.17
  - Information on Prospective Residents, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    5.36
  - Information on Proposed $24,250,000 One Year School Capital Improvement Program, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    11.15
  - Inlet Cluster Association, Reston, Virginia, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    7.16
  - Interim Report on Route 7, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    3.20
  - Issues Regarding "new town" New Franconia, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    7.03
  - Jack-in-the-Box Rezoning, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    9.01
  - Jack-in-the-Box: Letters on Proposals, Petitions and Acceptance, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    9.10
  - Jack-in-the-Box Memos, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    9.14
  - Jack T. Torregrossa Rezoning Application, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    5.35
  - Journal of the American Institute of Planners Volume 39 no. 5, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    11.12
  - Lake Fairfax Park Addition Tax Map, Centreville District, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    4.30
  - Letters, Miscellaneous, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    3.09
  - Letters Regarding Denial of Rezoning Application, 1970s (Box 5, Folder 10)
    5.34
  - Letter to Resident Community Association Chairmen and Members of the Board Regarding an Urge to Approve a Request for a Community Preschool, 1970s (Box 5, Folder 11)
    5.33
  - Letters on Clinch Corporation and Town Planning, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    4.26
  - Letter from Dockery Regarding Interest in Planning and Zoning, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    5.16
  - Letter on Gulf Reston Preliminary Plan, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    5.37
  - Letter from Daniel Smith and L. Lee Bean REgarding Brown's Chapel Joint Venture, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    5.41
  - Letters Concerning the Approving of Rezoning, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    4.02
  - Letters on Fairfax Zoning Case, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    4.24
  - Letters Regarding Development of Plans C-149, C-280-281, and B-230, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    6.11
  - Letter Regarding Route 28 and Beltway Road Request, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    .11
  - Letter to Mr. Robert Wilson and Lee Ruck from John Dockery, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    9.04
  - Lipnick Track, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    5.09
  - Low and Moderate Income Housing Inventory, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    2.14
  - Maps of North Shore Drive and Wlehle Avenue, 1970s (Box 5, Folder 23)
    10.09
  - Master Plan and Zoning Committee of Reston, Critique of Presentation Slips, 1970s (Box 5, Folder 24)
    4.10
  - Maps of Plans for Case S-168-71 to Fairfax County Planning Commission from Division of Land Use Administration, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    5.45
  - Master Plan and Zoning Committee Reston Community Association Minutes from Meeting, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    5.14
  - Master Xeroxes of Reston Maps, 1970s (Box 5, Folder 27)
    7.15
  - Memo for the Board of Explaining Background Philosophy and Answering Questions, 1970s (Box 5, Folder 28)
    3.15
  - Memo on New Site Plan and Memo from Chairman, 1970 and 1973 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    6.14
  - Memo on Outer Beltway and Traffic Patterns, 1970s (Box 5, Folder 30)
    4.19
  - Memo on Silver Core, 1970s (Box 5, Folder 31)
    5.07
  - Memo from Chairman of Reston Community Association Planning and Zoning Committee to Membership and Board Members, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    5.12
  - Memo on Subdivisions and Street Names, Recently Recorded and Site Plans Submitted, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    6.12
  - Memo Chairman, Reston Community Association Planning and Zoning Committee, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    11.17
  - Memo-Rezoning Case no. C-432, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    4.29
  - Memos on Reston Sewage, Taxes, Zoning and Population, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    9.15
  - Memo on Cases C-282, B-03, C-399, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    4.21
  - Memo on Reston Sewage, Taxes, Zoning and Population, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Memo from Chairman, Planning and Zoning Committee, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    5.18
  - Memo from Chairman, Planning and Zoning Committee, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    6.03
  - Memo from Chairman of Reston Community Association, Planning and Zoning Committee, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    5.13
  - Memo from Chairman, Planning and Zoning Committee, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    5.19
  - Memo from Chairman, Planning and Zoning Committee, 1973 and 1974 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    6.01
  - Memo from Chairman, Planning and Zoning Committee, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    5.11
  - Metropolitan Washington: Council of Governments, Regional Meeting for the Year 2000 Plan, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    3.16
  - Minutes from Reston Community Association Board Meeting, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    5.15
  - Newsletter on Route 7 Corridor Study with attached Letter to Dockery, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    5.29
  - News Articles on School Zoning, 1971 and 1972 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    10.05
  - New Communities Research Bulletin, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    3.01
  - Noise Exposure Forecast (Map) Bull Run and Upper Potomac District [Part 1], 1975 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    5.22
  - Noise Exposure Forecast (Map) Bull Run and Upper Potomac District [Part 2], 1975 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    5.23
  - Noise Exposure Forecast (Map) Bull Run and Upper Potomac District [Part 1], 1980 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    5.25
  - Noise Exposure Forecast (Map) Bull Run and Upper Potomac District [Part 2], 1980 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    5.26
  - Notice to Reston Community Association From Springfield Associates, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    6.09
  - Open Models for Reston, 1970s (Box 6, Folder 20)
    4.11
  - Open Space Study, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    3.18
  - Other Committees, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    7.05
  - Paddock Lane File, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    6.15
  - Parcel no. 132, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    3.05
  - Park Capital Improvement Program, Land Acquisitions and Development, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    3.21
  - Patio Homes Definition, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    11.08
  - Pending Rezoning Cases as of February, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    2.12
  - Planned Buildings and Appeals/Articles, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    7.01
  - Planners Notebook: Volume 1 no. 7, 5 and Volume 2 no. 3, 1971 and 1972 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    11.16
  - Planning Commission Meeting, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    4.22
  - Planning and Zoning Committee, Reston Community Written Analysis, 1970s (Box 6, Folder 31)
    4.09
  - Planning and Zoning Committee Notes, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    6.16
  - Planning and Zoning Committee Rezoning Cases, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    1.02
  - Preliminary Comprehensive Plan: Upper Potomac Planing District, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    7.09
  - Preliminary Comprehensive Plan of the Upper Potomac Planning District, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    2.01
  - Press Clippings, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    10.11
  - Printed Matter [Zoning Applications], 1972 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    7.12
  - Projection of Employment and Related Uses, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    2.11
  - Proposed Amendment to Chapter 30 (Zoning Ordinance) and Amendment to Article II, Section 30.2, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    5.06
  - Proposed Amendments, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    9.13
  - Proposal for Implementing an Improved Planning and Land Use Control System in Fairfax County, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    1.14
  - Proposal for Townhouse Private Streets and Other Amendments, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    6.02
  - Proposed Ordinance Amendment to Chapter 30 of the Zoning Ordinance (Article 13), 1972 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    11.20
  - Proposed Countywide Transportation Recommendation (Map), 1974 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    11.21
  - Quarter (Third and Fourth) Miscellaneous, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    7.04
  - Reports of Actions by the Fairfax County Board of Supervisors, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    7.02
  - The Report of the Study Team on Reston Institutions, 1970s (Box 7, Folder 16)
    8.06
  - Reston Center for Industry and Governance Declaration of Protective Covenants and Restrictions, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    3.10
  - Reston Center for Industry and Governance Declaration of Protective Covenants and Restrictions, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    1.04
  - Reston Community Association Letter on Issues for Upcoming Meeting and Cases of Rezoning, 1970s (Box 8, Folder 1)
    4.03
  - Reston Community Association Planning and Zoning Committee, 1970s (Box 8, Folder 2)
    2.02
  - Reston Community Association Analysis of Gulf Reston Plans for Future Development, 1970s (Box 8, Folder 3)
    2.06
  - Reston Community Association Letter on Major Rezoning of Route 7, 1970s (Box 8, Folder 4)
    5.30
  - Reston Community Association Position of Rezoning Petition, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    3.14
  - Reston Community Association, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    3.02
  - Reston Community Association Analysis of Gulf Reston Development Plans, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    10.13
  - Reston Community Association Letter on Cases, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    4.04
  - Reston Community Association Meeting Minutes, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    6.20
  - Reston Community Association Letter on Outer Beltway and Route 7 Impact Study, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    4.06
  - Reston Community Association Letter on Route 7 Master Plan, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    4.23
  - Reston Community Association Position on Case C-282 (Clinch Corporation), 1971 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    4.25
  - Reston Community Association Meeting on C-331 and C-342, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    5.02
  - Reston Community Association Board Meeting Minutes, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    5.03
  - Reston Community Association Outer Beltway and Route 7 Impact Study, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    5.49
  - Reston Community Association Letter of Denial of Case no. 2-168-71 Brown's Chapel Joint Venture, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    5.42
  - Reston Community Association Low and MOderate Income Housing and Rezoning Case C-149, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    5.38
  - Reston Community Association Letter in Regards to Cases, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    5.31
  - Reston Community Association Notes, Members Lists and Meeting Notes, 1971 and 1972 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    5.28
  - Reston Community Association Changes, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    7.14
  - Reston Community Association Application, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    2.05
  - Reston Community Association Residential Development Plans and Correspondence with Architecture Board Review, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    9.05
  - Reston Community Association Planning and Zoning Committee, Memos, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    9.16
  - Reston Community Association Meeting Minutes, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    9.12
  - Reston Community Association: Current and Planned Residential Construction in Reston, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    2.04
  - Reston Community Association Letter on Review of Rezoning Case C-282, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    4.01
  - Reston Community Association Case C-432 Gulf Reston to Rezone, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    4.27
  - Reston Community Association Letters on Rezoning Petitions, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    4.17
  - Reston Community Association: Meeting Minutes, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    6.19
  - Reston Community Association Letter on Cases C-399 and C-282, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    4.05
  - Reston Community Association Reston Critique, 1972 and 1973 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    9.03
  - Reston Community Association Reston REzoning Cases C-377 and C-378, 1972 and 1973 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    6.21
  - Reston Community Association Memos, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    10.03
  - Reston Community Association Planning of a Hospital in Reston, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    10.02
  - Reston Community Association: Five Year Countywide Development Program and Applications no. C-377 and C-378 for Rezoning, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    9.02
  - Reston Community Association: Meeting Minutes, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    6.18
  - Reston Community Association: Meeting Minutes, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    6.17
  - Reston Community Association: Meeting Minutes; John Dockery's Resignation Letter to the Reston Community Association Planning and Zoning Committee and Reston Community Association Bylaws, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    9.07
  - Reston Community Association, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    1.09
  - Reston Evaluation: Interim Report, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    11.02
  - Reston Home Owner Association Capital Facilities Study Steering Committee, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    3.17
  - Reston Home Owner Association Memos about Architectural Board of Review Meetings, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    9.08
  - Reston Housing Development and Blue Prints, 1970s (Box 10, Folder 2)
    4.20
  - Reston Maps and Reston Street Directory, 1970s (Box 10, Folder 3)
    5.27
  - Reston Master Plan Booklets, 1970s (Box 10, Folder 4)
    4.12
  - Reston Perimeter Development, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    8.07
  - Reston Times, Advertisements, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    5.46
  - Requests for Extensions of Time, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    11.10
  - Rezoning Application no. C-167 Filed by Gulf Reston Incorporation, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    6.10
  - Rezoning Application C-164, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    8.02
  - Rezoning Application C-359 by Richard T. Zeigler (Applicant), 1973 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    11.24
  - Rezoning Board of Zoning Adjustment (BZA) Application, Lester M. Markel (Applicant), 1973 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    11.23
  - Rezoning Cases in Hunter Woods Village, Reston Homeowners Association, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    2.10
  - Rezoning Case 76-C026, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    11.07
  - Rezoning: B-617 Henry J. Rolfs, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    1.12
  - Rezoning Memo, 1970s (Box 10, Folder 15)
    4.18
  - Role of the Reston Community Center (RCC) in Relation to the Church, 1970s (Box 10, Folder 16)
    2.03
  - Ryland Section, Paths (Soapstone to Lawyers Road), 1971 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    3.04
  - Sewer Allocations, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    8.01
  - Site Plans, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    11.22
  - Site Plan Related, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    11.05
  - Site Reviews by Paul Sternfels; Triangle Park, Townhouses and Burger Chef, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    6.05
  - Solid Waste Management Inventory, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    2.13
  - Staff Report Planning Commission and Rezoning Application no. C-280 and Amendment to B-555 and B-230, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    7.08
  - Staff Report Planning Commission, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    3.13
  - Staff Reports Planning Commission, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    5.04
  - Staff Report Planning Commission, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    4.15
  - Staff Report Planning Commission, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    4.16
  - Statement for the Environmental Management Committee of Reston Homeowners Association, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    2.07
  - Statement of Gene S. Bergoffen, Press. Reston Community Association, Before Fairfax County Planning Commission on Proposed Changes to Reston Comprehensive Plan and the Approved Development Plan for the Vicinity of the Hunters Woods Village Center and Rezoning Application, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    5.40
  - Statement of Reston Community Association Concerning the Proposal of the Reston Interfaith Housing Corporation to Develop Low Cost Housing in Reston, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    5.39
  - Storm Drainage Inventory, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    2.15
  - Study of Roles, Relationships and Processes in New Town Governance, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    11.13
  - Subdivision and Street Names, Memo: Road Improvements, Dodge Report and Letter to Reston Community Association Board Members from Sid Berman on Poor Meeting Attendance, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    6.07